{
    "id": "9fd77e52285d429f9b72a10eb5ca9881",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My father ……………….. for a brisk walk in the evening.",
            "description": "We use the simple present tense to talk about our habits and routines. ",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "goes",
                "is going"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………….. for Singapore next Monday.",
            "description": "We use the present continuous tense to talk about future events if the arrangement already exists.",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "are leaving",
                "have left"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I .......................... all my problems.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "solve",
                "have solved",
                "have solving"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We ................................. here for four years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are living",
                "have lived",
                "live",
                "have living"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ............................... a letter to my sister.",
            "description": "We use the present continuous tense to talk about actions or situations that are happening at the moment of speaking. ",
            "answers": [
                "write",
                "am writing",
                "writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………….. his breakfast when I reached his place.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was having",
                "is having",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ........................... him before.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "never saw",
                "have never seen",
                "are never seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. the minister last week.",
            "description": "We use the simple past tense to say that something happened in the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "meet",
                "am meeting",
                "have met",
                "met"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he ………………. the next day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will come",
                "would come",
                "was coming"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The letter ……………….. yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "posted",
                "was posted",
                "had posted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher ………………. the lazy boy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "scold",
                "scolded",
                "scolding"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. president of the club.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elected",
                "was elected",
                "has elected"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}